[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTING]
This is Mummy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA: Pen Pal.
NARRATOR: Peppa and her friends
are at playgroup.
Children,
who would like a pen pal?
ALL: Me!
Me!
[SNORTS]
What's a pen pal?
A pen pal is a boy or girl
you can write letters to.
This little girl lives
in France.
Her name is Delphine Donkey.
[SNORTS]
Can Delphine Donkey
be my pen pal?
Of course, Peppa.
Hooray!
[LAUGHS]
[HORN HONKING]
NARRATOR:
It is early morning.
Mr. Zebra the Postman
is delivering a letter
to Peppa's house.
Post!
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love it
when the post arrives.
[SNORTS]
It's addressed
to "Miss Peppa Pig."
That's me.
[SNORTS]
Mummy,
can you read it for me?
Of course.
It's from Delphine Donkey.
My pen pal!
[GIGGLES]
What does she say?
Bonjour, Peppa.
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Mummy, why are you
saying those funny words?
It's French, Peppa.
It means,
"Hello, how are you?"
What else does she say?
Hm.
I'll help.
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Heh-heh-heh. Clever Daddy.
[LAUGHS]
I am an expert in French.
[SNORTS]
What does it mean?
Um...
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig cleans his glasses,
so he can see
the letter more clearly.
Hm.
It's no good.
It's nonsense.
It means,
"I like fairy princesses
and playing
with my friends."
That's what
I was going to say.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I want to talk French.
Maybe you could talk
to Delphine Donkey.
How?
Her phone number
is on this letter.
Yippee!
[LAUGHING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
NARRATOR: Mummy Pig is asking
if Peppa may speak to Delphine.
Hello?
Bonjour.
Um...
[IN ENGLISH]
What do I say next?
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
[LAUGHS]
[IN ENGLISH]
Bye-bye.
[BOTH SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
[IN ENGLISH]
What did she say?
She spoke French.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Bonjour, George.
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is saying
"How are you?" in French.
Dine-Saw.
[GROWLS]
No, George.
That's not how you speak
French.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[HORN HONKING]
NARRATOR:
It is morning.
Mr. Zebra the Postman
is delivering letters
to Peppa's house.
Post!
Hooray!
Can I have my letter
from Delphine, please?
Sorry, Peppa,
there's no letter for you today.
Aw.
[DOORBELL RINGING]
I wonder who that could be.
Bonjour.
I am Delphine Donkey.
[BRAYS]
I have come to see Peppa.
It's Delphine!
Bonjour!
[SNORTS]
Bonjour, Peppa.
[BRAYS]
Here are my mama and papa
and my brother, Didier.
BOTH:
Bonjour.
[BOTH BRAY]
Here are my mommy and daddy
and my little brother,
George.
BOTH:
Hello.
Dine-Saw.
[GROWLS]
Dragon.
[ROARS]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[BRAYS]
Do you speak French,
Mr. Pig?
[SNORTS]
I'm an expert at French.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Um...
Yes.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Delphine, we could jump up
and down in muddy puddles.
NARRATOR: Delphine
does not understand Peppa.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
NARRATOR: Peppa does not
understand Delphine.
Everything's so different
in French, Daddy.
[BRAYS]
[IN ENGLISH]
Come on, Peppa.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Ah!
That's what I was going
to show you.
We call it jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
[LAUGHING]
[BRAYING]
J'adore jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
NARRATOR:
Everyone in the whole world
loves jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
[SNORTING]
[BRAYING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
Granny and Grandpa's Attic.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are playing
at Granny and Grandpa's house
today.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Grandpa Pig.
Papa Ig.
[CHUCKLES]
Hello, Peppa.
Hello, George.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
Bye-bye. See you later.
See you later.
[SNORTING]
[ENGINE STARTS
THEN HORN HONKS]
Where's Granny Pig?
GRANNY:
Hello, my little ones.
NARRATOR:
That is Granny Pig's voice.
But where is she?
Granny Pig?
[SNORTS]
Here I am.
Granny Pig!
Gangy Ig!
Why is Granny in the roof?
We're tidying the attic.
What's the attic?
It's where we keep
all our old things.
Like you, Grandpa Pig?
[LAUGHS]
Things that are even older
than me.
[LAUGHS]
Can we help?
[SNORTS]
Okay.
[LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Granny and Grandpa's attic
is at the very top
of the house.
That's the door
to the attic.
[SNORTS]
How do we get up there?
I have a clever trick.
Hello, my little ones.
It's Granny.
Come on up.
[CLANGING]
BOTH:
Ooh.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
This is our attic.
BOTH: Wow.
It's very full.
Yes, it's full of old junk.
[GRANDPA & GRANNY
LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Peppa and George are here
to help us
throw some things out.
Good. Let's start
by throwing out this box.
Oh! Not that box!
Do we really need this?
That's my ship in a bottle.
And this?
That's my other ship
in a bottle.
And these?
They're my other ships
in bottles.
I need them all.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Well, we have
to throw something out.
Uh, how about this box?
No. Not my hats.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oh, dear, we can't decide
what to throw out.
I know.
We'll let Peppa
and George decide.
Okay. Heh-heh-heh.
Let's throw away
this old case.
BOTH:
Aah! Not that one!
This isn't
just any old case.
It's a record player.
PEPPA & GEORGE:
Ooh.
And this
was our favorite record.
Can we play it?
Yes.
[LAUGHS]
We haven't heard it
for years.
['50s ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHS]
This takes me back.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Come on, Peppa and George,
let's dance.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[RECORD CONTINUES PLAYING]
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig is here
to pick up
Peppa and George.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hello?
Where are you?
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig cannot find anyone.
What's that noise?
[ALL LAUGHING]
PEPPA & GEORGE:
Mummy!
Hello.
[SNORTS]
We've been dancing
to Granny and Grandpa's
favorite record.
Yes.
Granny and Grandpa played it
all the time.
Ooh.
And here's the record
I used to play
when I was a little piggy.
PEPPA:
What is it?
It's called
"Birdie Birdie Woof Woof."
Not "Birdie Birdie Woof Woof."
You were always playing that.
I thought we'd thrown that out
ages ago.
[POP AND ZIP SOUND EFFECTS
PLAYING WITH MUSIC]
WOMAN: ♪ The birds go woof
And the dogs go tweet ♪
♪ Woof, tweet, woof, tweet
Woof, woof, woof ♪
♪ The sheep go moo
And the cows go baa ♪
♪ Moo, baa, woof, tweet
Woof, baa, moo, tweet ♪
♪ Woof, woof, woof ♪
[ALL LAUGHING]
Again, again!
[POP AND ZIP SOUND EFFECTS
PLAYING WITH MUSIC]
♪ The birds go woof ♪
♪ And the dogs go tweet ♪
♪ Woof, tweet
Woof, tweet ♪
♪ Woof, woof, woof ♪
♪ The sheep go moo ♪
♪ And the cows go baa ♪
♪ Moo, baa, woof, tweet ♪
♪ Woof, baa, moo, tweet ♪
♪ Woof, woof, woof ♪♪
[ALL LAUGHING]
That was fun.
But we were supposed
to be finding
some things to throw out.
Peppa, what should we throw out
and what should we keep?
Hm.
I think you should
keep everything.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
The Quarrel.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Suzy Sheep
are playing Snap.
Snap! I win.
[BOTH LAUGH]
NARRATOR: Peppa and Suzy
are best friends.
[BAAS]
Snap! I win again.
[LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
You cheated.
I did not.
You looked at the card.
[SNORTS]
I don't want to play
with you anymore.
[SNORTS]
I don't want
to play with you anymore.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
Peppa and Suzy
have had a quarrel.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
NARRATOR:
Mummy Sheep is here,
to take Suzy home.
Peppa, say bye-bye to Suzy.
[SNORTS]
I am not talking to her.
And I am not talking to her.
Oh. Ha, ha.
I'm sure they'll make it up.
They are best friends
really.
It is not funny.
We are not best friends
anymore.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is making supper.
Peppa! George!
Suppertime!
It's spaghetti!
[SNORTS AND CHUCKLES]
[SLURPING AND MUNCHING]
[SIGHS]
What's the matter, Peppa?
Peppa and Suzy
have had a little quarrel.
Oh.
[SNORTS]
But I do miss Suzy a bit.
Hm.
Let's give Suzy a call.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[RINGING]
[BAAS]
Hello, Mrs. Pig.
[SNORTS]
May Peppa talk with Suzy please?
Hello, Suzy.
Hello, Peppa.
We can be friends again,
if you say "sorry."
I'm sorry
I said you cheated.
Even though you did cheat.
Well, I'm sorry
you were ever my best friend.
[DIAL TONE HUMS]
Oh.
It doesn't matter.
I can easily find
a new best friend.
NARRATOR:
It is a lovely sunny day.
All the children
are at the playground.
Danny Dog
is on the roundabout,
with his best friend,
Pedro Pony.
BOTH:
Whee!
NARRATOR:
George is on the seesaw,
with his best friend,
Richard Rabbit.
Seesaw.
[BOTH LAUGH]
NARRATOR: Suzy Sheep is
on the swings, on her own.
[SIGHS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is playing mini golf,
on her own.
[SIGHS]
NARRATOR:
Here is Emily Elephant.
Can I have a go?
Yes.
[LAUGHING]
Emily, Suzy Sheep
is not my best friend anymore.
[SNORTS]
So you can be my best friend.
But my best friend
is Candy Cat.
Oh.
[MEOWS]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Whee!
Zoe, if you want,
you can be my best friend.
But my best friend
is Rebecca Rabbit.
Oh.
Whee!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
PEPPA [SNORTS]:
Hello, Suzy.
Hello, Peppa.
Ah, good.
I see you two
are friends again.
We are not friends.
We will never be friends
again.
Hm. I think it's about time
you two made it up.
Peppa, say sorry to Suzy.
Only if she says sorry
first.
DADDY PIG:
I know.
I'll count to three
and you can both say sorry
at the same time.
BOTH:
All right.
DADDY PIG:
One, two, three.
BOTH [IN UNISON]:
Sorry.
Now you can be
best friends again.
BOTH:
Hooray!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Suzy, let's play
mini golf.
Good idea.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Suzy
are best friends again.
Me first.
My go.
My ball went in the hole,
so I win.
But my ball knocked it in,
You're just
making the rules up.
You were
I win!
No, I win!
[DADDY PIG LAUGHS]
You two are just the same.
[CHUCKLES]
That's why
Suzy is my best friend
in the whole world.
[LAUGHS]
And Peppa is my best friend
in the whole world, ever.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
The Toy Cupboard.
NARRATOR: It is Peppa
and George's bedtime.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Goodness me.
Why are all these toys
on your bed?
[SNORTS]
That's where they live.
Quickly, put the toys away
in your toy basket.
But the toy basket is full.
MUMMY PIG:
Oh, so it is.
Maybe you need
a toy cupboard.
Yes. I could make one tomorrow.
[SNORTS]
The last thing you made,
Daddy Pig,
was this shelf.
I am very proud
of that shelf.
But, Daddy, it's all wobbly.
[SNORTS]
We use it as a slide.
For Teddy and Mr. Dinosaur.
[ALL LAUGHING]
All right, let's buy
a new toy cupboard.
We can buy one now,
on the computer.
Hooray!
[SNORTING]
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig is using the computer
to buy a toy cupboard.
Ah-ha.
Now, which one shall we get?
Can we have this one, please?
MUMMY PIG:
That looks perfect.
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig is buying
the toy cupboard.
[CASH REGISTER RINGS]
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Congratulations.
Your toy cupboard
is ordered.
Oh, goody.
[♪♪♪]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
NARRATOR: It is morning,
and Mr. Zebra the Postman
has a special delivery.
[HORN HONKING]
Post!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Special delivery
for Miss Peppa Pig
and Master George.
What is it?
It's a toy cupboard.
Oh. It looks a bit flat.
Yes. You build it yourself.
Oh.
Don't worry, Peppa.
It'll be very easy
for your mommy and daddy
to build. Goodbye.
BOTH:
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Now what do we do?
Now we build
your toy cupboard.
Yes.
[BOTH LAUGH]
That's strange.
There aren't
any instructions.
Maybe it's so easy to build
it doesn't need
instructions.
[SNORTS]
Mummy, can we help?
Yes.
First I need a shelf.
[GIGGLING]
Here's a green shelf.
Thank you, Peppa.
Now I need four legs.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
One, two, three, four.
Four blue legs, Mummy.
Lovely. We'll have this done
in no time.
Here's a red door,
Mummy Pig.
Thank you, Daddy Pig.
There. Finished.
Well done, Mummy Pig.
It's very tiny.
How will all our toys
fit inside?
It is a little small.
[SNORTING]
Oh.
George has found another bit.
Uh...
Maybe that's a spare shelf.
And there's
all these bits too.
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear, the cupboard is tiny
because Mummy Pig
has not used all the pieces.
We'll just have to take it apart
and start again.
Oh, no.
If only we had
the instructions.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Who can that be?
Hello.
I've just found this in my van.
It's the missing
instructions.
That will make things
a lot easier.
Hooray!
[SNORTING]
[GROANS]
NARRATOR:
The instructions look
very complicated.
It's no good.
It's nonsense.
Leave it to me, Daddy Pig.
I quite enjoy
putting these things together.
Really?
[SNORTS]
Can we help in any way?
You can put the kettle on.
I'll have a nice cup of tea
with six sugars, please.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Everyone is preparing tea
and biscuits
for Mr. Zebra.
Teatime, Mr. Zebra.
Wow!
NARRATOR:
Mr. Zebra has built
the toy cupboard.
My goodness, that was quick.
Yes, and I've put all your toys
in there too.
BOTH:
Ooh.
[SNORTS]
Thank you, Mr. Zebra.
[SNORTING]
But there's no room
for these last two.
Oh. Poor Teddy
and Mr. Dinosaur.
Where are they
going to live?
Why not simply order another
easy-to-make cupboard?
No!
I've got a better idea.
Teddy and Mr. Dinosaur
can live on your beds.
But, Mummy,
that's where they lived before.
Yes, I know.
That's why
it's such a good idea.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING AND SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND GIGGLING]
[SNORTING AND LAUGHING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪